Closing Ceremony
Congratulations on your win, Suiryu!
We had a minor incident toward the end,
but in the end, you won,
completely unscathed!
Unscathed?
If he hadn't pulled his punch, I would've...
Announcement
We now have an announcement
for everyone here.
There appear to be monsters
outside right now,
Monsters?
so we ask that you do not leave the
venue until the police give the all-clear.
Again?
We'll be safe from the monsters in here.
True.
There's no point in dwelling on it.
I just need to make sure
I never see that guy again.
Hey, you're cute.
Huh?
I'm just going to take it easy.
What's that?!
What is that?!
M-Monsters?!
Look! They're holding
Rosie, Dave, and Bazuzu!
The contestants that were
sent to the hospital..
I-I'm outta here!
You guys can deal with the monsters!
See ya!
Hey!
Are all the contestants here?
Look at all you runts. How far
the martial arts world has fallen...
Well, whatever.
You're all going to become monsters.
The Strong Ones Fight Back
Even you trash fighters should be somewhat
useful after you become monsters.
Become monsters?
We pro heroes will put you in your place!
Way to go, heroes! Kick his ass!
Finished already?
With one hit?
I'm not here to kill you all today.
I'm Goketsu, and I'm here on behalf
of the Monster Association.
Goketsu?!
You don't mean the previous
Super Fight champion?!
If you know who I am,
this shouldn't take too long.
You must realize resistance is futile.
But I heard that he was killed
by a monster a few years ago!
So why...
It's true that I was defeated by
a certain monster in the past,
and I was taken to their lair.
But to my surprise, they made me an offer.
In return for my cooperation,
they would grant all of my desires!
As a monster, I can surpass
the limits I had as a human!
Do you understand what I'm saying? Right now,
I'm on a completely different level
than the martial artist Goketsu!
Rejoice! I have something to give you.
Eat those monster cells.
Then you can all become monsters.
If you don't eat them, I'll just kill you.
The Monster Association...
What do you want? Are you just
out for murder and destruction?
True, violence is a basic
desire for monsters.
But that is not our only motive.
We're trying to go one step higher.
You can just stay there and watch for now,
and observe how physically and
mentally weak humans are.
Choose.
Die or become monsters.
No, don't!
This is amazing!
I can feel the power and
violence flow through me!
Hey, fatso!
You're gonna regret what you
did to me during our match!
He's got superhuman strength now.
How interesting that even a peasant
like him could gain such power.
I should be able to awaken
to the ultimate power,
given I'm the man with the
world's most perfect genes.
Choze, not you, too!
Not only did it improve
my physical functioning,
but I can feel my subconscious
limits falling away.
So this is how it feels to be
a monster? Let's see...
Jakumen!
Now I'll definitely be able to kill that guy!
I'll make him pay for embarrassing
me like that... with his death!
You didn't turn out too bad.
We do have winners and losers,
depending on what we're working with.
Go on. The rest of you filth
need to eat those, too.
Please, spare me!
Benpats!
This is for survival.
Hamukichi!
This is to become stronger!
Not you, too, Boltane!
I feel like I can do anything now!
This feels great!
They all turned into monsters!
Wh-Wh-What should we do?
Hey.
If I can chase those guys off,
will you go on a date with me?
Great! That settles it.
I'm going to relieve all that stress
from the finals right now.
Oh? We actually have someone who
dares defy us in this situation?
So be it.
We're to eliminate anyone who dares to
become an enemy of the Monster Association.
Finish him!
You fool! You're nothing but a playboy!
You suddenly want to play hero now?
That's not it.
It's just that you guys
are in the way...
of my fun lifestyle.
Well, well... You're not half bad.
Not half bad?
Your answer suggests you lack intelligence.
What's that?
I've decided.
I'll remake this world with only
those of my own choosing.
And all of you fail.
Begone.
This is nothing!
What?!
And in my eyes, you just failed.
Entertain me a little more.
You fool!
They're too fast! I can't see anything!
Dark Body Quake Tiger Fist!
Dark Body Phoenix Rising Fist!
Way to go!
Ouch... I haven't bled in a long time.
This "monsterization" stuff sure is wild.
They all became way stronger.
You know, it would be a
waste to just kill you.
I'll still let you change your mind.
The world will eventually
belong to the monsters.
That means the strong can
go as crazy as they want,
kill all they want, and enjoy true freedom.
It'll be a world of blood and violence.
You can live an enjoyable life as a monster.
Not a bad deal, is it?
Don't tell me...
I see.
You're saying it doesn't matter
what the world's like,
as long as you enjoy yourself...
Well, sorry... but the last thing
I ever want to be is as ugly as you!
Dark Body Flying Dragon Fist!
Yes!
Then you get to die.
Watchdog Man!
You're awesome!
Thank you!
You really are the guardian deity of City Q!
I guess he really is a Class S hero.
Just before I started my hunt,
monsters suddenly attacked.
I was amazed at how powerful
and fast he was in that battle,
but it's nothing.
I can deal with him just fine.
Watchdog Man, it's your turn to be hunted!
Are you human, or are you a monster?
Fist of Flowing Water Crushed Rock!
I didn't say, "Shake!"
He does have speed and
power, if nothing else.
But he's inhuman!
What? You done already?
Stand up. I'll give you three seconds.
Three, two, one...
Good, good... Keep fighting back,
as if your life depends on it!
it... He's not even flinching.
What do I do?
You can take care of those guys, too.
Well, this isn't good...
Come on, now, pay attention!
It broke...
Well? What's the matter?
Stand up. I'll give you three seconds.
Three, two, one...
Dark Body Quake Tiger Fist!
H-He caught my strongest attack?!
He's strong...
He surpasses me in every way...
S-So this is... a monster?
Hey, guys. You get some good grub today.
Enjoy your meal!
They were my disciples.
But they were mentally weak,
so when they turned into monsters,
they lost their sense of self.
!
This isn't good!
Hey, you! I'm in trouble here!
Lend me a hand!
Suiryu.
After observing the finals,
I've realized that you're stronger than me.
There's no way that I can
beat you. I'll admit that.
But now, you're on the verge of death.
How ironic.
You may have taken the top
position in human society,
but you don't stand a chance
against these monsters.
That's why I'm asking for your help!
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to become a monster, as well.
You can just die right here.
I give up on becoming the
world's strongest person.
I'll aim to be the ultimate
being on the next level!
Ah, he actually ate all of them.
You greedy villain.
Shut up! I'll shut that trap
of yours myself in a moment.
Looks like your body's not holding up.
You've failed to become a monster.
Now, then... You're
finally the only one left.
Hero Association Hospital
There are patients up ahead in
the ICU that can't be moved!
As a hero, I can't back down!
In the end, heroes are only human.
You're only worth being
oppressed by us monsters.
Everyone ran off,
or they were defeated.
Good for you. Now you can cry and
scream without anyone seeing you.
Go on. Let me hear you scream.
Coiling Defense!
Lightning Kick!
Snek! Max!
You're okay!
But why... Why did you come back?
To help.
Now that we're dressed like
this, we're the real deal.
This suit is strong against
monster claws, fangs, and beaks.
It's a battle suit!
I'm also wearing my lightning shoes!
Now we can really show
you what we're made of!
We're up against three opponents, though.
Can we leave one of them to you?
Yeah!
You guys are lifesavers. Thank you!
Tank-Top Tackle!
That was an amazing tackle...
Don't try so hard when you're
not wearing a tank-top.
Can you stand, Mumen Rider?
Yeah.
I sure can.
All right... My legs can still move.
Now, let's get out of here.
Why are you taking fighting
stances, you two?
We'll hold him back.
Use that chance to run.
You can't be serious!
You guys don't stand a chance!
I mean, you two were lower than me...
You're kidding... Aren't you scared?
This is my last chance!
I need to run! Run! Run! Run!
Where do you think you're going?!
Things are just getting interesting!
Oh? I guess this one was a winner after all.
It looks like you're the same
threat level as me: Dragon.
Of course I am!
Oh? You're still trying to stand?
Our first objective...
Let the monsters run wild to show
the humans how terrifying we are.
That part is going very well.
No place is safe anymore.
Everything is enveloped
in uneasiness and fear.
Objective number two...
Kidnapping someone connected
to the Hero Association.
That was also a success.
We managed to kidnap the son
of one of their executives.
And objective number three...
Turning worthy humans into monsters.
This is also going well.
Nyaan infiltrated a prison
and monsterized a bunch of violent
inmates, and is heading back here.
It appears Goketsu has turned some of
the martial artists into monsters, as well.
That should also bring us
some worthy monsters.
It appears Goketsu is still...
Hey, Goketsu. Come back.
If multiple Class S heroes show up,
even you will end up with broken bones.
Don't underestimate me.
But I'm done here, anyway.
Hey, newbie.
Huh?
I'll take you to our hideout. Come with me.
Don't you dare order me around!
Just listen.
There are a number of monsters,
including me, who are stronger than you.
Don't let your head get too big.
Are the other monsters heading
back to the hideout, as well?
That means the heroes,
including Class S heroes,
will head toward any remaining monsters.
A simpleton like you
wouldn't stand a chance.
I've given you a warning.
Now, I'm heading back.
The outskirts of City Z.
That's where you can find us.
Did you hear that, Suiryu?
There's a ton of monsters.
Hilarious, isn't it?
That guy's punch freaked me out.
Yeah, I'm done trying to be the strongest.
S-Say, Bakuzan...
I have no intention of fighting anymore.
Please... Just let me go.
You see, Suiryu...
S-Stop...
I've always been a guy who loved
hurting those weaker than me!
That's the only reason I
wanted to become stronger!
Now that I'm free, I feel great!
Let's go for another!
Wow, the great Suiryu
actually screamed in agony.
It's too bad we don't have
an audience to witness this.
Youth, talent, popularity,
money, women, and freedom.
Don't you think you're a bit
greedy to have all of that?
I'll let you taste a bit of hell
before you die to make up for it!
You're pathetic, Champion.
Someone!
Help me!
A monster!
There's a monster here!
Isn't there anyone who can help me?!
I'm being attacked by a monster!
Please!
Heroes... Right! Heroes!
If you can hear me, please come here!
Heroes! Please come!
There's a monster here...
Heroes...
No one's going to hear you.
No heroes are going to come.
You're going to die!
No one stands a chance against this guy...
No matter how strong some heroes may be...
But, please... Rise up once again...
When people find themselves in
darkness, they seek the light.
It doesn't matter how faint
or small that light is.
As long as it's there, there's hope...
This is what you call despair.
Who are you?
I'm a hero.
I heard you call for help, Suiryu.
You did well on your own.
Leave the rest to me.
The Ultimate Dilemma